singsale.com.sg 2015-05-29

# Singsale.com.sg - Privacy

SINGSALE.COM.SG, referred to in this Privacy Policy as the “Website”, is an online retailer of consumer goods operated by Ozsale Pty Limited (ABN 11 118 610 987) (“Ozsale”), a company registered in Australia.

In this Privacy Policy, "we" or "us" mean Ozsale and its affiliates and subsidiaries, including Singsale Pte. Ltd., which provides settlement and customer services on behalf of Ozsale in Singapore; and "you" means the user and/or customer of the Website.

Ozsale values our relationship with you and the other users of this Website. We recognize that you may be concerned about our collection, use, and disclosure of your personally identifiable information that we may collect when you use the Website. Accordingly, we have implemented this Privacy Policy to inform you of the information that we collect from you, how we collect this information, and what we do with it after we collect it. If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us via our contact us page, email contactus@singsale.com.sg or call +65 6842 2919.

If you wish to unsubscribe from our daily notifications you can do so by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any of our email notifications or by visiting www.singsale.com.sg/unsubscribe.aspx.

Singsale is located at; Block 3 Kallang Sector #05-03 Singapore 349278

## Membership Registration

Our Website's registration form requires you to provide us with your contact information and may also require your demographic information. We may use your contact information from the registration form to send you information about our company and the services we offer. Your contact information is also used to contact you when necessary.

## Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored in a browser-related file on your computer's hard drive when you use this Website. We use cookies to improve the members’ experience. We also use them to deliver information and fresh content specific to your interests. Cookies are widely used on most major websites.

We mostly use "session" cookies, which are removed from your computer once you leave the Website. These cookies are used so our system can remember that you have logged in already and prevent you doing so necessarily. The technology we use (Microsoft.NET), requires the use of session cookies. Session cookies expire and are deleted after 30 minutes of no activity on the Website.

The Website also uses persistent cookies to personalise the user experience, to help protect our members and to provide us with research information (such as how often members visit the Website each month). Persistent cookies allow us to track users on the Website and help us identify users abusing any of the services available on the Website.

## Payment Information  

Your personal information is treated with the greatest of care. Sensitive payment information such as credit card details are NEVER stored on the Internet and our system.

## Ozsale's Commitment to Online Security  

In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures (such as the use of an industry standard secure https connection) to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.  Payments and other transactions on the Website are processed via an industry standard secure https connection using Citicorp Payment Services, Inc. as a third party payment gateway. This means that you can be assured that your sensitive data such as credit card numbers will remain confidential because all information is 128bit encrypted. The server we connect to is authenticated through PKI certificates issued by a root Certificate Authority. Our payment page is also fully PCI DSS compliant please visit https://www.pcisecuritystandards.org/tech/for more information.

## How Your Information May Be Shared  

We never sell or rent your personal information. We may release personal information under the following circumstances:  

  * Where release is required by law (for example, a subpoena) or regulation or is requested by a government agency
  * Where our records indicate a company or an individual may be engaged in fraudulent activity or other deceptive practices that a governmental agency should be made aware of;
  * To appropriate persons, where your communication suggests possible harm to others.
  * To our affiliates and subsidiaries (some of which are based outside of Singapore) who may use and disclose your information for the same or similar purposes as us.
  * To facilitate the sale or other disposition of our business.
  * For carrying out marketing and products analysis and marketing our and our affiliates’ or subsidiaries’ products and services.  

## Members Right to Access and Correct Personal Information

You have the right to access the Website to correct your personal information held by us provided the information is held in a way that can be readily retrieved. You can access and correct your personal information under the “My Account” section of the Website.  Alternatively you can send us an email via the section “My Contacts” in your “My Account” of the Website.  

## Invite a friend

We provide facilities throughout the Website to refer friends to the Website. You may not use the "Invite a friend" service or other email forwarding services that we offer to send spam or otherwise send content that would violate our Privacy Policy or Terms and Conditions. We do not permanently store, sell, or rent these email messages or the email addresses.

## Third Party Links  

The Website may contain links to third party sites. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected on the Website, and we shall not be held liable for any claim arising out of your dealings and transactions with these third parties who are accessible through and linked from the Website.  

## Passwords

You are responsible for all actions taken with your user name, email address and password. Therefore we do not recommend that you disclose your password to any third parties. If you choose to share your user name, email address and password or your information with third parties for whatever reason, you are responsible for all actions taken with this information and therefore you should review that third party's privacy policy.  

## Membership Removal

If you wish to be removed from our database for any reason, simply send us an email requesting to be removed via the section “My Contacts” in your “My Account” of the Website, or our “Contact Us” page.

## Updates to our information practices

Ozsale reserves the right to amend the terms of this Privacy Policy from time to time without prior notice because of changes in Internet technology and applicable laws. Whilst we will make every reasonable effort to notify you of any changes to this Privacy Policy, you are advised to check this Privacy Policy periodically to update yourself on any changes and apprise yourself of the then applicable Privacy Policy.

Current version of the Privacy Policy effective as of 1 March 2012.
